Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/surjitsingh7 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Deep Learning
Python (Programming Language)
Machine Learning

Certifications

Designing RESTful APIs

Surjit Singh

Deep Learning || Machine Learning || NLP || Python || Rest & Fast API || Bert Model || Text Classification

Chandigarh

Summary

Surjit Singh is an adaptable professional who specializes in problemsolving, good communication, and strong analytical skill. Rich Experience in Machine Learning, Deep learning, and hands on experience in building Rest API with Flask and Django.

Professional Skills and Interests:

- Machine learning
- Flask and Django Developer
- Deep Learning(NLP-NER)
- · Data structure and Algorithms
- Data Science and Data analysis
- · Understanding of Databases and SQL
- · Multiple programming paradigms

Experience

enrichdata.io Software Engineer (ML) January 2021 - Present (1 year 6 months)

Natural Language Processing | Deep Learning | Restful API | Flask

Excellence Technology
Flask & Django Training
May 2020 - October 2020 (6 months)
Sahibzada Ajit Singh Nagar, Punjab, India

Flask || Django || Rest API || Fast API || GUI ||

Education

CHANDIGARH UNIVERSITY

Master of Computer Applications (MCA), Computer Science · (2018 - 2020)

Chandigarh Group Of Colleges

Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA), Computer Science · (2015 - 2018)

Government Senior Secondary School, Rajpura Intermediate · (2013 - 2015)

Shiva Ji Model Senior Secondary School Matriculation · (2012 - 2013)